Rollo run test 07: Square test N=2
Realtime speed
01. Forward movement
Motion capture: Red marker; Extended Kalman filter: Blue marker; Odometry model: Green marker
Movement is done according to a specified time value, since direct odometry readings are not available.
02. Turning 90°clockwise
03. Forward movement
04. Turning 90°clockwise
05. Forward movement
06. Turning 90°clockwise
07. Forward movement
This turn was the worst so far. Often it is the result of uneven surface of the laboratory.
08. Turning 90°clockwise
Square run 1 is finished. Square run 2 starts.
09. Turning around
10. Forward movement
Motion capture lost the Rollo again. There was a recent recalibration of the whole motion capture system.
11. Turning 90°counterclockwise
12. Forward movement
Motion capture data available again.
13. Turning 90°counterclockwise
14. Forward movement
15. Turning 90°counterclockwise
16. Forward movement
17. Turning 90°counterclockwise
18. Full stop
Square run 2 is finished. The initial position indicated by the blue marker. Offset is approximately by 3 m.