Rollo run test 08: Square test N=1
Realtime speed
01. Forward movement
Motion capture: Red marker; Extended Kalman filter: Blue marker; Odometry model: Green marker
Movement is done according to a specified time value, since direct odometry readings are not available.
02. Turning 90째clockwise
The rotation is clockwise, even though the visualization node indicates the opposite. This is due to recent calibration of system.
The visualization node was corrected afterwards.
03. Forward movement
04. Turning 90째clockwise
05. Forward movement
Too much rotation. Depending on grip and opposite force the rotation speed of Rollo changes drastically.
06. Turning 90째clockwise
07. Forward movement
08. Turning 90째clockwise
09. Full stop
Square run 1 is finished. Position is off by approximately 2 m.