ROS environment startup
Realtime speed
Using the manual approach where all nodes have to be started manually.
Only motion capture mocap_optitrack node is executed using launcher.
All nodes accept parameters. They are specific to the function of the node.
Communication node is started first.
Since there is connection to control node, the emergency procedure is executed.
Once the connection is established communication node continues to run in normal operation mode.
Preprocesser node is started. Notice that there is no output. This is due to lacking data from motion capture node.
Extended Kalman filter node is started. Since there is no input data, the estimates stay at a specific value.
The publish.sh script will be used to read logs and publish the data within using rostopic.
Start of visualization node.
Rollo is at origin of the coordinate system of motion capture.
Script for publishing is started. Preprocessor node receives data from mocap_optitrack node.
The actual position of Rollo is displayed. The odometry model has not been updated. The EKF node would have to be restarted for that.
Demonstration of different possibilities of the visualization node.
Different marker scale and frequency rate of visualization node are used.
Different refresh period of the plot is being used. Here movements can be tracked more easily at the cost of performance of the node.
Demonstration of the control node. Pay attention to the output of communication node in the top right terminal.
Again display of the emergency procedure of the communication node.