ROS environment startup using launcher
Realtime speed
Using the launcher approach to start all nodes.
This includes running the mocap_optitrack node as a dependency.
All output is to the screen. Using "output=log" in the launcher would prevent that.
All nodes are color coded for easier recognition by user.
The publish.sh script is being used to read logs and publish the data within using rostopic.
Once the data is available the position from motion capture and EKF are updated, but not the odometry model.
Command ros-jade loads the environment for that particular version of ROS.
Control node is not critical to operation of the system. It starts running in this terminal and the one started by launcher is killed.
Communication node is critical however. So after starting it in another terminal the one from launcher will be killed.
This terminates the whole launcher. All nodes exit, except the external ones.
The reason for the delay was that visualization node starts another process to omit plt.show() commands restrictions. This prevent from clean exit. User interaction is needed.